Hey everyone, this is EYA on EYA
Censored Supernatural Bible Changes on
YouTube.
And today is Monday,
the 8th of April. Excuse me, the 8th of
May, 2022.
This was sent to me by our sister
Rebecca, and I just thought I would do a
quick video to show you what she sent to
me. She took a image of two of her
Bibles side by side.
It looks like one is a King James Bible,
and the other one, which is what you're
looking at right here, is a different
translation.
But friends, the books of the Bible
were the same across translations.
You know, like Genesis,
right? Exodus, Numbers, 1 Corinthians, 2
Corinthians, you know, and so forth.
We are seeing
the titles to various books of the Bible
are changing.
So, I know the last book of the Bible to
be Revelations.
This particular Bible says the
Revelation
of Jesus Christ. Let me go ahead and see
if I can zoom in here. The Revelation of
Jesus Christ. Here is her King James
Bible,
and we've talked about this change
before on my channel.
This is from her King James Bible, which
now says the Revelation of Saint John
the Divine.
Well, first of all, brothers and
sisters, there is only one who is divine
whoever walked this earth.
It's not you,
it's not me, and it's not John.
His name was Jesus Christ.
But now, the title to this
book of the Bible
in the King James Bible
now alludes
that there is another one who is divine
who walked the earth.
Saint John the Divine.
It's time to wake up in Jesus name.
Our Bibles are under savage attack
and supernaturally changing preparing
the way
for the Antichrist and coming world
satanic system.
Our Bibles have prolific changes on
every single page of scripture.
Doctrinal errors, nonsense verses
new words, gibberish, emoticons,
italicized words, new people, modern
words, words omitted, words added.
It's a new book. It's unfamiliar.
It's time to wake up in Jesus name.
Let me know what your title
says for
the Book of Revelations in your King
James Bible. Go look.
And you tell me in the comment below
what your Bible says.
You can also email me an image at
eyareport
@gmail.
I'd like to see it.
Friends, if you do not know Jesus Christ
as your Lord and Savior, let today be
the day of salvation for you. If you
walked away from the Lord
this is your time to come back to him.
We are seeing Bible prophecy happen
right now. We are seeing lying signs and
wonders.
And we were warned of this hour.
Scriptures always indicated that
something like this would happen. We
just didn't have eyes to see.
Jesus Christ is the king of kings and
the lord of lords and unless you are
born again, you will not enter the
kingdom of heaven.
Ask Jesus Christ for the forgiveness of
your sins and confess Jesus Christ as
your lord and savior.
The moment that you ask Jesus Christ
for the forgiveness of sins and confess
him as your lord and savior, the son of
God,
miraculous work will take place
and he will give you a new heart
and give you a desire for righteousness.
And you will know the truth and the
truth will set you free.
Be strong and courageous, brothers and
sisters. Do not fear be dismayed for the
lord your God is with you wherever you
go. Until next time.